A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Records and Institutional Support, 1985-1995; 2
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Smith, Michael, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1940)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Takhounts, Marie Westbrook, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1941)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Tursunov, Akbar, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1942)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Vashenko, Alexander, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1943)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Wade, Rex, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1944)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Cartwright, Kimberly, 1995 Fall (Box 121, Folder 1945)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Creuziger, Clementine, 1995 Fall (Box 121, Folder 1946)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Ezzo, Joseph, 1995 Fall (Box 121, Folder 1947)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Gungoren, Billur, 1995 Fall (Box 121, Folder 1948)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Hershatter, Gail, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1949)
    Joint proposal with Wendy Brown.
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Howland, Marie, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1950)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Maslach, Christina, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1951)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - McLeod, James, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1952)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Stuart, Robert, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1953)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Swietochowski, Tadeusz, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1954)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Applicant List, 1995 Fall (Box 122, Folder 1955)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Amherst College, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 1887)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Amherst College - Final Report, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 1888)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Teachers College, Columbia University, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1889)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Hoover Institution, Stanford University, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1890)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Indiana University, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1891)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Library of Congress, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1892-1893)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - New York Public Library, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1894)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Stanford University, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1895)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Michigan, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1896)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1992 (Box 119, Folder 1897)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Columbia University, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 1898)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 1899)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - St. Vladimir's Seminary, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 1900)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1993 (Box 119, Folder 1901)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Illinois, 1993 (Box 119, Folder 1902)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Kansas, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 1903)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Minnesota, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 1904)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - University of Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 1905)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Grant Reports (1992 Awards), 1992-1994 (Box 120, Folder 1906)
  - JCSSS - Program to Alleviate Backlogs - Grant Reports (1993 Awards), 1993-1996 (Box 120, Folder 1907)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Columbia University, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 1158)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Latvian Studies Center Library and Western Michigan University, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 1159)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - New School for Social Research, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 1160)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), 1992 (Box 85, Folder 1161)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - University of Kansas, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 1162)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - University of Notre Dame, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1163)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - University of Wisconsin-Madison (Rzhevsky Collection), 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1164)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Utah State University, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1165)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Yale University, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1166)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Radio Free Europe - Radio Liberty (RFE-RL), 1993 (Box 86, Folder 1167)
  - Program to Alleviate Backlogs (Declinations) - Rutgers University, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 1168)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Alexeev, Michael, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1169)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Berkowitz, Daniel, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1170)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Flaherty, Patrick, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1171)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Gaddy, Clifford, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1172)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Gora, Marek, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1173)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Gronicki, Miroslav (Participant Observer), 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 1174)
    A notation on the original folder indicates that Gronicki also participated in the 1990 workshop.
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Hopkins, Barbara E., 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1175)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Ickes, Barry, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 1176)
    A notation on the original folder indicates that Ickes also participated in the 1990 workshop.
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Koshevoy, Gleb A., 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1177)
    Folder also includes a 26-page "preliminary draft" of Michael Alexeev and Barry Ickes paper on "Equilibrium 'Goods Runs' in Soviet-Type Economies."
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Kuznetsov, Yevgeny, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1178)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Litwack, John, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1179)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Lu, Ding, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1180)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Milobedzki, Pavel, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1181)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Mitchell, Janet, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1182)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - MItchneck, Beth, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1183)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Mladek, Jan, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1184)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Moltz, James Clay, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1185)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Murphy, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 87, Folder 1186)
    Murphy participated in the 1989 workshop and was a participant observer in 1990.
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Nikul'nikov, Igor, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1187)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Plich, Mariusz, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1188)
    File also includes a paper by Marek Gora and Michal Rutkowski on Demand for Labor and the Disguised Unemployment in Poland in the 80s.
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Quinn, Kathleen, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1189)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Reiman, Marki, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1190)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Roberts, Bryan, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1191)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Spagat, Michael, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1192)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Vodopivec, Milan, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1193)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics - Lotspeich, Richard (Withdrew), 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1194)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Acharya, Arnab, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1195)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Adshead, Thomas, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1196)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Biessen, Guido, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1197)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Bim, Alexander, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 1198)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Bloemsma, Johanna, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1199)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Drummond, William, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1200)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Jarmoszko, A. Tomasz, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1201)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Kabala, Stanley, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1202)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Krovak, Jiri, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1203)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - McDonald, Jason, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1204)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - O'del, John, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1205)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Richardson, Craig, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1206)
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Schepina, Irina Naumovna, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1207)
    Name also spelled Shchepina.
  - Workshop on Soviet and East European Economics (Declinations) - Strzalkowski, Piotr, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1208)
- Fellowship Records - Declinations (Graduate Training, Dissertation, and Postdoctoral Fellowships), 1990-1991, 1993-1995; 3
  The Fellowship Records - Declinations subseries contains the Title VIII fellowship application files for individuals who were not selected for funding in the annual Title VIII fellowship rounds. The records are arranged by year and by fellowship program, namely graduate training, dissertation fellowships, and postdoctoral fellowships.
  There are no Title VIII fellowship declination files for 1992; the subseries is also missing dissertation fellowship declinations for 1991 and 1995.
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Allen, Howard Douglas, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1209)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Andrews, Josephine T., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1210)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Barletta, Michael, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1211)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Becker, Jonathan A., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1212)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Bernstein, Frances Lee, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1213)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Birkenes, Robert M., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1214)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Bogoslaw, Laurence H., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1215)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Boilard, Steve D., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1216)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Brennan, Page Herrlinger, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1217)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Brody, Richard, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1218)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Carleton, Gregory S., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1219)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Cunningham, Mary K., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1220)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Daly, Brooke Y., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1221)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Drummond, William J., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1222)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Economy, Elizabeth C., 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1223)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Ericson, Joel Meyer, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1224)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Essaides, George (Box 88, Folder 1225)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Geraci, Robert P., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1226)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Goldman, Philip S., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1227)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Hale, Henry Ewing, V, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1228)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Hatch, Warren F., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1229)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Herman, Robert Gary, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1230)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Jones, Susan, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1231)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kahn, Daniel S., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1232)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kamp, Marianne Ruth (Box 89, Folder 1233)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Kizenko, Nadieszda, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1234)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Knight, Nathaniel, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1235)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Manchester, Laurie, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1236)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Norlander, David John, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1237)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Olsen, Jonathan Robert, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1238)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - O'Neill, Craig, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1239)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Peris, Daniel, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1240)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Poole, Randall, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1241)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Porter, Brian, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1242)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Roberts, Bryan Wilson, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1243)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Roslof, Edward E., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1244)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Rusnock, K. Andrea, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1245)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Schoenberg, Robert Paul, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1246)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Sedaitis, Judith, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1247)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Shmelev, Anatol V., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1248)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Siena, Matthew, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1249)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Sil, Rudra, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1250)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Slepyan, Kenneth, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1251)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Smith, Kathleen E., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1252)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Speckhard, Michael, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1253)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Stern, Richard E., 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1254)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Stoecker, Sally Webb, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1255)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Stulberg, Adam, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1256)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Tadjbakhsh, Shahrbanou, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1257)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Thorson, Carla, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1258)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Tyson, David, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1259)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Wells, Ludmilla, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1260)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Ballard, Elza Perry, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1261)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Bellows, Heather, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1262)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Bruckner, Scott, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1263)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Carnaghan, Ellen, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1264)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Cohen, Ariel, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1265)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Coler, Elena, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1266)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Comer, William John, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1267)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Daley, Tad, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1268)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Dannehl, Charles, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1269)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - De Nevers, Renee M., 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1270)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Duskin, James Eric, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1271)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Eby, Pauline P., 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1272)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Elleman, Bruce, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1273)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Epstein, Lisa Rae, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1274)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Faeges, Russell, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1275)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Fajer, Lubov, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1276)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Furtado, Charles Francis, Jr., 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1277)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Gordon, Ellen J., 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1278)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Granville, Johanna, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1279)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Grigorian, Stella, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1280)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hamilton, Ellen L., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1281)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Harrison, Richard, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1282)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Heiser, Meredith Ann, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1283)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Holl, Bruce, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1284)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Hopkins, Barbara Ellen, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1285)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Horowitz, Brian, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1286)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Ilgenfritz, Craig Alan, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1287)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Kaufmann, Andrew F., Jr., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1288)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Krancberg, Sigmund, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1289)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Lempert, David H., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1290)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Machula, Casey, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1291)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Mansour, Lawrence, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1292)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - McGrath, Troy Douglas, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1293)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Meisel, Maude, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1294)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - MIller, Burton Richard, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1295)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Miller-Pogacar, Anesa, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1296)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Mirsky-Zayas, Irina, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1297)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Mueller, Julie Kay, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1298)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Murat, Aman Berdi, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1299)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Nelson, Amy, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1300)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Nesbet, Anne, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1301)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Newman, Sally, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1302)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Paine, Sarah C., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1303)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Pavlovszky, Maria, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1304)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Petersen, Roger D., 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1305)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Sande, Anita Gail, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1306)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Sankovitch, Natasha, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1307)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Schecter, Kate, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1308)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Sedik, David, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1309)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Sell, George, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1310)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Shengold, David L., 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1311)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Sherlock, Thomas, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1312)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Smith, Michael Gerard, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1313)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Titlar, Linda, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1314)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Twigg, Judyth, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1315)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Valdez, Jonathan Carl, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1316)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Venable, Sondra, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1317)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Watson, Samuel Edgar, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1318)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Wehling, Fred L., 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1319)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Wlodek, Steven, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1320)
  - Dissertation Fellowships (Declinations) - Zebroski, Robert, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1321)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Argenbright, Robert, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1322)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Borden, Richard Chandler, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1323)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Cavanagh, Clare, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1324)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Chester, Pamela, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1325)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Cook, Linda, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1326)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Forrester, Sibelan, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1327)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Frank, Stephen, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 1328)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Hoffman, David, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1329)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kirss, Tiina, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1330)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Kustanovich, Konstantin, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1331)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Levitt, Marcus, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1332)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Liber, George, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1333)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Lotspeich, Richard, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1334)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Mandelker, Amy, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1335)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Moses, Russell Leigh, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1336)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Naydan, Michael, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1337)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - NIchols, Thomas (Finalist), 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1338)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Oswald-Koenigsknecht, Laura, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1339)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Reese, Roger, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1340)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Ruttenburgh, Nancy (Finalist), 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1341)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Schwartz, Lee R., 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1342)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Siegel, Katherine, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1343)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Stavrakis, Peter, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1344)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Straus, Kenneth (Finalist), 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1345)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Tomei, Christine, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1346)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships (Declinations) - Van Geldern, James, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 1347)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Altoma, Reef, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1348)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Amsden, Elizabeth, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1349)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Amsden, Elizabeth, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1349 A)
    Restricted - Health information - Open in 2091.
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Bell, James, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1350)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Bogoslaw, Laurence, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1351)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Buchli, Victor (Alternate 4), 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1352)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Cahn, Jennifer, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1353)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Corbesero, Susan, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1354)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Deess, Eugene, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1355)
  - Graduate Training (Declinations) - Doggett, Suzanna, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 1356)